Hi jazz, I'm Marie McGillard,
and I'm excited to apply as a virtual assistant role,
which will be includes and with less.
What interests me about this opportunity is to support growing business
and help improve daily operation and organization and communication through
a vision system. I have experience as a virtual assistant,
supporting e-commerce, balance, Contemporary Asians and doing
admin tasks and also social media management and doing CRM
spreadsheet and tracking workflows including the applicator
I also have experience as a TikTok affiliate manager
where I reconnect with the content for the editors and monitor
the performance about our product and help support the brand float My
technical skills include can pass,
Shopify, Google Workspace and also Spreadsheet,
and chat GBP and Cloud and other AA tools.
The head that helps me improve productivity and workflows.
I'm someone who learns quickly and takes the ownership of tasks
and proactively communicate and enjoy finding ways to
make the process smoother. I'm looking for the long-term opportunity where
I can contribute to the team and blowing passionately and I want
to take you for the opportunity and I'm looking forward to speaking with you.
Thank you Jazz.